https://www.redboxvoice.com/privacy-policy#cookies

Quantify
Search & ReplayLive AcquireEvent ReconstructQuality ManagementInsightAgent Controls
Services
APIsTranscriptionSalesforce IntegrationMicrosoft Integration
Government
ARE YOU COMPLIANT?
Become a Reseller
SPECIALIST REQUIREMENT?
QUANTIFY
Search & ReplayLive AcquireEvent ReconstructQuality ManagementInsightAgent Controls
SERVICES
APIsTranscriptionSalesforce IntegrationMicrosoft Integration
Our Privacy & Cookie Policy
This privacy policy aims to give you information on how Red Box collects and processes your personal data through your use of this website, including any data you may provide through this website when you make an enquiry, sign up to our newsletter, purchase a product or service or take part in a competition.
This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.
It is important that you read this privacy policy together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This privacy policy supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.
All data handled by Red Box Recorders will be done so in accordance with UK data protection principles, that is to say it will be
Processed fairly and lawfully
Obtained for a specific purpose and only handled as such
Adequate, relevant and not excessive in relation to the purpose it was obtained for
Accurate and, where necessary, up to date
Kept only for as long as is necessary for the purpose it was obtained for
Processed in accordance with your rights
Kept safe and secure
Kept within the EEA unless an adequate level of data processing protection is ensured
Read the below headings to find out more.
Q
WHO ARE RED BOX RECORDERS AND HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US?
A
Red Box Recorders Limited Incorporated and registered in England and Wales with company number 04186453 our registered office is:
Bradmore Business Park,Loughborough Road,Bradmore,Nottingham,NG11 6AQ
If you have any requests concerning your personal information or any queries with regard to these practices please contact us by post to the above address, by email to enquiries@redboxrecorders.com or by telephone to +44115 937 7100 or through this website via our contact us page.
Resources
Q
HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
A
We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances: –
Identifying potential customers, resellers or partners.
Dealing with your requests and enquiries.
Providing you with information about products and services we offer.
Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
Collecting your application for employment at Red Box Recorders (please refer to our human resources privacy policy for more information on how this data is handled.).
Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.
Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.
We do not sell personal information collected through this site or use your personal information for any other purposes than those stated above.
Resources
Q
WHAT ARE THE LEGAL GROUNDS FOR HANDLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
A
Data protection laws describe the legal bases that we can rely on to process your personal data, and below we set out the legal bases that we rely on to do so.
Necessary for the performance of a contract or to comply with law
In most cases, we collect your personal data because you want to, or have, purchased products or services from us and processing of your data is necessary in order to perform the contract we have with you. Where we need to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of a contract we have with you and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you. In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us but we will notify you if this is the case at the time. In particular, we may rely on this legal basis for processing in the following scenarios:-
To enable you to access detailed information about our products on our website and use our services.
To let you know about significant changes to our product, terms or privacy policy.
To confirm your identity and authenticate the information you provide about your company.
To provide and improve the support we provide to you or your company.
To send you company communications and resources (if you are a customer, channel reseller, distributor or partner).
Consent
Where we collect other information from you such as when we use cookies to collect information about the device you use to access our website, you will be asked to consent to this before using our website. If you choose not to give your consent, or you later remove your consent, this may affect our ability to provide information to you.
We may also rely on consent in the following scenarios but consent will be proactively requested at the point of collection and we will make it clear what you are consenting to and explain what we intend to do with the information being provided.
Marketing – from time to time, we would like to let you know about products, services and offers from Red Box Recorders
Market research – we may send you invitations to participate in market research.
Administration of prize draws, competitions, membership offers, surveys and other promotional activities.
Necessary in our legitimate interests or those of a third party
We can also use personal information for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) as long as those interests are not outweighed by your interests, and fundamental rights. examples of where we may relay on legitimate interest include:-
Complying with/supporting compliance with legal and regulatory requirements – we must comply with various legal and regulatory requirements. Additionally, the services we provide help other organisations to comply with their own legal and regulatory obligations. For example, some of our customers are regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority.
Internal training purposes – to enable us to train our staff to better provide services to our customers.
Reporting and analytical purposes – to provide management information and information to improve our products and services.
Tracking activity – to help us to improve our services.
To maintain our records and other administrative purposes.
Complaint and dispute resolution – we will need to use personal data when looking into queries and complaints.
Email tracking – to improve our communications to our customers, resellers and partners.
Invitations to participate in market research – in order to improve the service, we may ask you to participate in research for time to time.
Resources
Q
KEEPING YOUR INFORMATION SECURE
A
We have put in place appropriate security measures to prevent your personal data from being accidentally lost, used or accessed in an unauthorised way, altered or disclosed. In addition, we limit access to your personal data to those employees, agents, contractors and other third parties who have a business need to know. They will only process your personal data on our instructions and they are subject to a duty of confidentiality.
We have put in place procedures to deal with any suspected personal data breach and will notify you and any applicable regulator of a breach where we are legally required to do so.
Who we share your personal information with
We share your personal information only with the people who need to handle it so we can provide the Red Box products and services you enquire about or procured. We also share it with:
Our staff engaged in providing you with products and services.
Suppliers who provide us with products and services or support to our IT tools and systems.
Resellers, distributors and partners involved in delivering the products and services we provide. For example, if you make an enquiry through this web site about purchasing our products and services directly, we may pass your details to one of our trusted resellers who will contact you about your enquiry.
Resources
Q
WHERE IN THE WORLD DO WE SEND YOUR INFORMATION
A
We may share your personal data with our staff, resellers, suppliers and partners located outside of the U.K. This may involve transferring your data outside the European Economic Area (EEA).Whenever we transfer your personal data out of the EEA, we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by ensuring at least one of the following safeguards is implemented:
We will only transfer your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission.
Where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in the EU.
Where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them pursuant to the Standard Contractual Clauses (also known as the EU Model Clauses) as mandated by the European Commission, or an appropriate derogation under Article 49.
Please contact us if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA.
Resources
Q
YOUR RIGHTS TO KNOW HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION
A
It is important that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and current. Please keep us informed if your personal information changes.
Under certain circumstances, you have rights under data protection laws in relation to your personal data.
Request access to your personal data.
Request correction of your personal data.
Request erasure of your personal data.
Object to processing of your personal data.
Request restriction of processing your personal data.
Request transfer of your personal data.
Right to withdraw consent.
You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by contacting us at any time. Where you opt out of receiving marketing messages, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result you purchasing any of our products or services.
No fee usually requiredYou will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights). However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.
What we may need from you?We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and ensure your right to access your personal data (or to exercise any of your other rights). This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response.
Time limit to respondWe try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated.
Resources
Q
HOW LONG WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION FOR
A
We will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary to fulfil the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements.
To determine the appropriate retention period for personal data, we consider the amount, nature, and sensitivity of the personal data, the potential risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure of your personal data, the purposes for which we process your personal data and whether we can achieve those purposes through other means, and the applicable legal requirements.
Details of retention periods for different aspects of your personal data are available in our retention policy which you can request by contacting us.
Resources
Q
USE OF COOKIES
A
Cookies may be used by us to provide you with customised information from our web site. A cookie is an element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. Cookies allow us to understand who has seen which pages and advertisements, to determine how frequently particular pages are visited and to determine the most popular areas of our web site. Cookies may also allow us to make our web site more user friendly.
We use cookies so that we can give you a better experience when you return to our web site. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. You do not have to accept cookies, and you should read the information that came with your browser software to see how you can set up your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, this will give you the opportunity to decide whether to accept it. If you disable cookies from your browser you may not be able to access certain features of a particular website.
For more information about cookies and how to manage them please click here
Resources
Q
SOCIAL MEDIA
A
Some pages of this site carry social media links in the form of buttons to external services or websites, such as Twitter, Facebook, LinkedIn and ShareThis. These allow users to share content or access additional content about Red Box Recorders. Be aware that these websites may also use cookies to collect information about you. Please check these websites’ privacy policies to see how they collect or use your information.
Resources
Q
CHANGES TO THIS POLICY
A
Red Box Recorders reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting changes online. It is your responsibility to refer to this privacy policy on accessing this site.
Resources
Request a Demo
UK Headquarters
Bradmore Business Park
Loughborough Road
Bradmore
Nottingham NG11 6QA
+44 (0)115 93 77 100
Please keep me up to date with news, events and offers from Red Box.
Thank you for submitting your details. Press the button below to download your asset.
DOWNLOAD
